this is a voice coin toolbox it allows
you to clone the voice of someone from
only five seconds of audio and to
synthesize speech with that same voice
really really was impressed for them I
thought that they did so well and it was
a tough final you know I think there's a
way to measure the acute emotional
intelligence that has never gone out of
style things that don't work and you
just kind of barrel through it you know
you get through it
yeah there's a way to measure the acute
emotional intelligence that has never
gone out of style and the other thing
also was the format of the show there's
a way to measure the acute emotional
intelligence that has never gone out of
style the toolbox is cross-platform you
can use audio files on your desk for
reference or existing data set such as
library speech and Vox Ella you're also
free to record audio yourself when
selecting a dataset a random speaker
will be selected as well as a random
utterance from that speaker click loud
to load the islands in the toolbox you
can then play it but now and then on
some just occasion for vivid interest or
wholesome indignation once you load an
utterance you can see it's Mel
spectrogram and a representation of its
embedding the embedding is a numerical
representation of the voice if you loud
enough utterances in the toolbox you
will be able to see a 2d space
projection of all embeddings loaded
embeddings from distinct speakers will
form separate clusters let's select a
new speaker to see that
you can see that the two speakers from
distinct clusters the mole that creates
the embeddings is not aware of the
identity of the speakers so the
clustering is entirely based on the
characteristics of the voice I can
record my own speech a few times to
create my own embeddings
when you record an utterance the toolbox
you played back to you things when
you're recording them it is good to have
at least three utterances from the same
speaker in order to see clusters appear
with this last segment my cluster should
now become separate from the rest a
slight segment my cluster is now here
and you can see that is far from the
other speakers because my voice has
distinct characteristics you could use
the system for user identification
through voice on the plot of the most
recent embedding you can see that the
same speaker will have some common
patterns let's take a random speaker and
now the few advances you can see that
this speaker for example tends to
activate this value and this value for a
slice you have an embedding loaded you
can synthesize a voice the synthesizer
is in charge of generating your mouth
spectrum from the given embedding and
the text prompt here you are free to
write anything to be synthesized however
there are a couple of limitations the
synthesizer was trained on datasets of
audiobooks therefore its tone may not be
very natural for conversation also the
datasets did not contain punctuation so
it will be ignored for now you must
insert line breaks to mark poses I'm
hoping to improve that in the future
let's take the abstract of the paper
this toolbox is based on as reference
text when you click on synthesized take
a try on the synthesizer will generate a
mouth spectrogram of the speech clicking
several times will generate slightly
different speech tucked in actual audio
you need to run the vocoder first let's
listen to the voice the speech is based
on point your telescope in such a
direction at such a time and you will
see a new planet hitherto unknown to man
this must if a coder runs in sub linear
time with respect to the length of the
input so it's more efficient on long
sentences you can see the real time
factor here we describe a neural network
based system for text to speech
synthesis that is able to generate
speech audio the voice of different
speakers including those unseen during
trainings our system consists of three
independently trained components a
speaker encounter network trained on the
speaker verification task using an
independent data set of noisy speech
without transcripts from thousands of
speakers to generate a fixed dimensional
embedding vector from only seconds of
reference speech from a target speaker a
sequence the sequence synthesis Network
based on taciturn - that generates a mel
spectrogram from text conditioned on the
speaker embedding an autoregressive
wavelet base for gutter network that
converts the mel spectrogram into time
domain waveform samples now that you
have generated this utterance the
embedding will also be computed you can
see the synthesized embedding in the
projections as they are represented with
a cross if the voice cloning was good
then the cross should be close to the
cluster of the same speaker father
remembered that you will need at least
three utterances from the same source
for fair judgment you can also select
Griffin him as the vocoder it is not a
deep learning mall but it will run
faster for sure input and will generate
less parasites than the preacher in the
coder however it will lose many
characteristics of the voice this is an
example of a sentence generated with
Griffin 'ln this is an example of a
sentence generated with Griffin limb
this is an example of a sentence
generated with Griffin limb you will see
that the griffin in generated utterances
will form a distinct luster you can
observe the symphony man with the
pre-trained vocoder without cluster
should be much closer to ground truth
advances thank you for watching I hope
you enjoyed this project